We became idols today.
And we're filming our glitter to create a movie.
A self-supported idol movie.
What the camera captures is
sparkles and timidity of our girlhood.
And our purity.
Let us tell our story as a movie.
(Devotion to Cinema)
An audition for maidens in love
I'll apply for it in my birthday suit
My specialty is
a blood-stained love letter
I'm worried if you don't like it
Taking a walk in shades with round shoulders,
I feel like
I'm a pottery buried in soil
Although I'm a girl
with a heart too timid,
We'll go location-scouting
of love in bare feet
Please find me!
And my dream without makeup
If I don't show who I really am,
It will just be a blooper
Please look at
my real performance,
Words of love in monotone
Find them all in
the screen of your heart!
Director and Story by Noboru Iguchi
A few months ago
Choo-choo, choo-choo...
Wait!
Don't leave me behind.
Carry me in your memories.
We cannot resist the torrent of time.
You're no longer an existence on earth.
As an evidence,
I can't touch you even if I want to!
Someone is holding me hard from the inside!
NO!!
I'll make it explode.
BAAAANG!
Well, can you play the scene up to here again?
Hey, that "BAAANG" was awesome.
What a nice ad-lib.
You perform everything heartily, Yoshie.
It almost sounds sarcastic, Moe.
Well, I just thought everything needs vigor.
How was it?
It was cute, but...
Yes, you could suppress it a little.
Too much overacting may draw
the play into a wrong direction.
Well, I thought emphasizing
will make it more understandable.
I agree with you, Yoshie.
Your lines are too difficult
to understand, President.
I don't think I have to
make them understandable.
I don't want to cheapen
the main character's feelings.
I'm disgusted. It sounds like I'm the cheap one.
No, you don't mean that, do you?
An acting that conveys nothing is meaningless.
Do it again.
I don't understand.
Let's play the next scene.
President.
Can I have a word?
What is it?
What's up?
Well, I'll quit the drama club
at the end of this month.
Why?
I can't tell you now.
I'll send you a text.
I want to hear it now.
I'll send you a text later.
Oh, what will become of our drama club?
I'm surprised to hear Moe's quitting.
Well, but I understand Moe's feelings.
Our president is too arrogant.
Although she criticizes our performances
a number of times, her script is only partially finished.
No?
Well, yes.
Well, Kazuko, you're our only junior.
You're not quitting, do you?
Well, but...
I'm sorry for acting selfishly.
But I'm taking Kazuko away with me.
A drama company of my acquaintance
will let us help them.
Is that true?
You too should be off with the president soon.
Don't waste your adolescence in vain!
What? What?
What on earth is it?
Oh, what're we gonna do?
We can't perform with only three members!
Calm, please calm down.
It's a punishment for our president.
Her body is large, but her mind is
too occupied with small things.
When our practice is finished,
she goes home without any follow-up.
It's a punishment for her doing only
what she wants to do with her heart shut to anyone.
And the president of the drama company is so great!
Oh, I'm so curious!
I love how he directs the plays
and he got many prizes.
Bye.
I'm really looking forward to it!
What are you going to do, Akari?
I partially understand
what our president wants to express,
and I don't dislike her seriousness.
I'll follow her.
Really?
I agree with you if you say so.
Sure, we've been together ever
since we were in junior-high.
I'm so happy!
I'm comfortable when you're beside me.
Me, too!
I'm so glad!
I'll be always with you, Akari!
Akari, you're so warm!
Today's math teacher,
the teacher who speaks with a slit...
The way he pronounces "s" is almost like...
Can you understand what he's saying?
I feel happy when I'm with Akari.
We're laying a bet on
which of us will get a good husband,
but all I want is to be with Akari for good.
I think I understand everything about Akari.
Everything.
Well, is there someone?
No, there's no one.
Okay.
Yoshie, are you still in the drama club?
Yeah, sort of.
Well, can you introduce some of the members?
What do you mean?
I've told you, one of my friends in the university
is filming independent movies.
Well, I remembered.
She wants real high-school girls
to perform for one day.
Nope.
Why not?
I'm not saying YOU have to perform.
Well, it sounds quite tiresome,
and our club is too occupied for that.
Find someone else.
How dare you talk like that?
Ouch!
Stop it! What's that?
It's tiresome for me, too!
But I'm trying to set it up because she insists!
Then why don't you turn it down?
Attack me more, and I'll scream to call our dad!
Yoshie, why don't you stop using
the Kansai dialect though you're in Tokyo?
It's been three years
since you tumbled into this house.
Your schoolmates will find you bothering.
Get someone. Absolutely!
I didn't tumble into this house!
I had no choice because our mom died!
It's so tough.
President, this is a relief
until we get new members.
Just take it easy. Easy.
Akari!
Thanks for coming!
Long time no see.
I'm Yoshie's elder sister, Keiko.
I appreciate everything you do for her.
Your sister's kind and beautiful as ever!
Oh, no, no. Don't be deceived.
She's an angel only when she's outside.
Yoshie, let me introduce Naomi.
Naomi, are you ready?
Yes, I'm coming soon.
Is she the director?
Yuck, she looks exactly like
a classy student of an art university.
I don't think I can get acquainted with her.
Nice to meet you. I'm Naomi Kunikida.
I'm making pieces with Yoshie's sister
in the visual arts department.
I wanted real high-school girls
to star in our latest movie,
so I decided to call you.
Thank you so much.
Are you interested in movies?
Yes, very much.
How about you, Yoshie?
Well, can I have a word?
Go ahead.
You call it a movie, but it won't be released
all over Japan, will it?
It's just your assignment.
Yoshie.
Yes, it is.
But I'll apply for the movie festival.
Well, I have a question.
Why does it have to be real high-school girls?
I don't want to lie even if it's a movie.
In this movie,
I'd like to explore changes that occurs
when girls in their adolescence confront with each other.
Like I observe fish in a fish tank.
We're not fish.
That's insulting.
Let's go!
Hey, Yoshie!
That's true!
It may be just our assignment.
But having contact with elders will be a good chance
to learn about yourselves that you don't know.
No, Yoshie?
Read it.
Oh, this script only describes the situation,
and almost everything is up to ad-libs!
And it'll never finish within one day!
My sister has deceived me!
Did you all look at Naomi's eyes?
I can't express it very well,
but they had a strange aura.
I felt that, too.
Her eyes had an mocking air,
as if they're saying "You can't do it."
So I find turning down the offer is
a little humiliating.
No, President. Don't be provoked by her!
Okay?
Aki!
Aki?
Wait! Wait!
Oh, no. We've lost her.
Hey, don't you worry?
I do worry, but it can't be helped.
She can take care of herself.
By the way, I'm feeling hungry.
Why don't you come to my house?
Well, I have to go home....
No, don't go home.
Stay with me today....
Oh, our staff got into the frame!
Cut, cut! Let's check the film.
Check the film.
Please have some tea.
You got in the frame, go that way!
Oh, my sister's acting was so stiff.
Was it?
Nice work!
I feel nervous to play in front of a camera!
But you were good.
And there're so many staffs.
You should have done it, President!
No, I'll just pass.
Sorry, can you do it again?
You were looking at the lens for a moment.
I'm sorry.
Keiko.
Keiko,
such an overdramatic
but superficial acting is useless.
Do you understand love?
Yes.
How is it different from fancy?
I... I don't know.
I only have a vague idea.
Be a woman extremely afraid of love.
Release more juice from your pores.
Keiko, you have no loneliness flooding from your body.
Dark stare, dark stare.
Well, but...
as I read the script,
I find my role ordinarily cheerful.
If you think so, your reading is shallow.
Looking at your acting is far less interesting
than looking at one's own private parts.
Isn't that so?
Expose yourself.
Reveal your naked heart.
Let's film another take.
Yes.
Yuck, this is the first morning of filming
and the atmosphere is already awful.
Just unbelievable.
Yoshie, you were laughing at me, weren't you?
Scene five, cut two, take one.
Ready, action!
Maybe I'd better go home.
No, please don't go!
Cut!
It was good... prostrating yourself.
Quite agreeable.
Is it?
Great, great. That prostrating was great.
But let your role possess you more.
Let the moment of your deepest despair possess you.
Ready, action!
NO! DON'T GO!
Ouch, please stop!
That's it! Let's take off your pants of your heart.
Pants, pants, yes, pants.
Now, let your soul be completely naked!
Don't go!
Come on!
Naked!
Good, good, good, good!
Further, further!
That's it, that's it.
Cut!
That was close.
Did you feel exactly like when you were despaired?
When I was ten,
my mother bought cake only for my younger sister.
I recalled that.
That's it.
My sister is getting awful.
And is Akari all right?
Akari, let's act as forcefully as Keiko.
Yes.
Acting is like playing a catch.
If your co-actor plays the masochist,
play the sadist.
It's okay to hit her.
Yes, I understand.
OK, let's film one more take
before we wrap up.
One more take!
Final take!
Ready, action!
Maybe I'd better go home.
No.
I DON'T ACCEPT THAT!!
Are you all right?
DON'T TOUCH ME!
OH, NO!
My sister's broken!
NO! NO!
Are you all right?
Don't stop her!
Let her continue!
NO!
Director, Keiko's bleeding from her head!
Cut!
That was great!
Your acting was more compelling,
and the way your skirt flapped was so good.
Oh, yes?
Although I ended up bleeding,
you praise the way my skirt flapped.
No.
I said your acting was good.
You praise the way my skirt flapped over me!
A live action is inferior to mere cloth!
I've told you, I don't mean that.
Excuse me.
As I'm bleeding from my head,
- Can you call a taxi to take me to the hospital...
- Wait, wait.
Take this.
OK, let's change the location.
That's no good.
Akari!
Are you all right?
Did I do unnecessary acting?
Is it my fault?
All right, all right.
You don't have to worry, Akari.
OK? It's all right. Just calm down.
Just breathe. Slowly.
I'll go look for her.
Sister?
Sister!
Sorry for saying that in a complicated way.
Well, you directed the camera only to Akari....
You misunderstand me.
She and my sister were in
THAT sort of relationship....
All right?
Akari, don't see that.
Don't hear that.
What's the matter?
This is no good. Absolutely no good. Run!
What's going on?
Wait a minute. What happened, really?
This movie is no good.
Definitely no good.
I'll make excuses, so just drop out of it.
But some scenes are already completed,
and I don't feel like giving up in the middle.
But...
Also, I have a keener instinct than others do.
Something tells me we should continue.
It's like a magnetic wave.
I feel the contrary. I'm afraid.
I fear something's gonna take you away.
Why don't we stay in a family restaurant?
I don't want to meet my sister.
Yes, of course. We're friends.
Yoshie,
I've kept it a secret,
but I really can see many things.
My future, someone who's already passed away.
A part of me believes that
such things will guide me.
Oh, I just can't stand it.
But it's fine with me.
Because of that, I can be
close to you like this in your house.
Cut!
Okay, cut.
What's this? I'm letting you use my house.
Don't put your luggage here!
I'm sorry, I forgot to take your band-aid off.
I'm gonna do it now.
Hey, why are you taking it off?
I thought it would make the scenes incoherent.
This is okay.
I don't want this movie to fit into ordinary categorization.
I want to take things as they are into my piece.
Besides, don't touch my actress without permission.
All right.
Do whatever you like.
Sorry, may I interrupt?
Akari.
In the next scene....
She may be thinking of your role as more than a friend.
Yes, I understand.
She probably wants to get closer to you.
I understand.
Maybe she fancies your role.
Yes.
What's she gonna do to you?
Well...
A kiss... maybe....
Yes.
Show me your natural feeling,
how far you can accept.
Okay, let's roll the camera.
Yes.
I have a bad feeling.
Ready, action!
Can you guess what I'm thinking of?
Sort of.
Shall I tell you?
Yes.
Akari, that's good. That's the way.
That's the way to go. Great.
This is no good.
Why do you stop me!?
No.
Akari, that's good, that's good.
Just go for it. That's it.
Go on, go on.
That's good, Akari. That's the way.
That's the way to go.
Just go for it.
What's the matter?
Just continue, this is going very well.
I can't.
Just continue.
No!
Okay, cut.
Let's change the mood and do it again.
Wait a minute!
Aren't you going too far?
You made her play the kiss scene by leading questions.
It's just ridiculous!
Is it?
It's natural if you're absorbed in your role's emotions.
That's sophistry.
You just want to make Akari kiss!
Are you jealous?
I'm not jealous!
No one wants to see her sister
kissing her best friend in her own house!
It has nothing to do with one who shoots a film.
Does it?
I couldn't kiss her,
because I realized I'm just a tool
for filming such scenes.
What are you saying?
Keiko, you're an actress!
Before being an actress,
I'm your lover, Director!
I'm the one you're going steady with!
I can't play this role any more!
I can't! I don't want to!
Why are you laughing!?
Come this way!
Ouch! Let go of me!
What do you want with me? Stop it, Sis!
So, what are we gonna do?
Yeah.
We'll just go on, of course.
Aren't you insane?
How can we go on when the actress has dropped out?
We still have an actress, the president of the drama club!
What? Me?
No, I've never performed as an actress!
You don't need experience, if you have a sensitivity!
Oh, I can't bear it any more!
May I go home?
Yes, you may.
Male staffs are useless. They've no guts.
Wait.
Only female staffs are to remain.
Agreed?
Yes.
Hey, may I talk?
Can you officially take part?
We'll start filming now.
But...
We'll abandon what we've filmed so far.
I want to make my movie a conceptual art
that changes in accordance with the situation.
I have an instinct that
you can understand this role better.
Maybe you can be who you truly are
in front of the camera.
Can't you?
Stop taking your anger out on me, Sis!
Can you understand the agony of being a lesbian?
Of seeing
the one you love lusting for someone else?
I can!
I'm feeling them right now.
I may not be a lesbian,
but I'm feeling agony too!
It's your bad habit to believe
you're the only one who's in pain!
Ready, action!
Well,
Watashi...
(Female form of "I")
No, boku...
(Male form of "I")
I have gender identity disorder.
Though I have a female body,
my heart is a male's one.
And I have fancied you as an opposite sex.
I couldn't tell you for a long time.
Is this your performance?
Cut!
OK!
It was great!
I could see the bottoms of your hearts.
Wait, Yoshie. Why do you ignore me?
It was just a film shooting!
Beware!
That trick won't do!
Oh, yeah?
Well, I do it too frequently.
What have brought you here?
Well....
When Mom and our brother Asei
died in the accident...
you resisted in tears,
insisting that you'd live in Osaka with grandma.
I'm sorry for saying you tumbled into this house.
You don't have to apologize.
Asei was a funny brother.
Hey, take a look.
What is this?
This is a movie Naomi directed three years ago.
She wears our school uniform.
Yeah, we all graduated from your school.
Then why doesn't Naomi ask this actress to perform?
It's impossible.
She has been killed.
Killed!?
Her name is Ayano Kogure,
and she was three years senior to Naomi.
Naomi was filming a parody of idol movies
with Ayano playing the lead.
Look at another actress.
This is Naomi!
Yes.
Naomi was filming the movie only with Ayano,
but before the filming was completed,
Ayano has been killed by her boyfriend
whom she wanted to break up with.
This is it!
I found the trump card to take a trick on Naomi!
Yeah, it looks it's going well.
That's the way, hang in there!
OK? This is on your way back from school.
You'll make certain your feelings toward each other.
No lines required.
Show your natural emotions.
Yoshie?
Hey, you two, what have brought you here
all of a sudden?
Sorry to interrupt you during the filming.
My sister has some business with you.
Maybe it's too late,
but I'd like to perform in your movie.
I desperately want to.
- Sorry, but half of the filming is finished.
- You said your movie can mutate, didn't you?
If your movie is a conceptual art,
a new character would bring in unexpected turn of events.
Yeah, you're right.
But does everyone agree?
Agree?
Yes.
I'd rather highly approve it.
That settles it!
Yeah!
But it'll be an impromptu one-shot filming.
Don't stop acting.
Okay, ready, action!
Well...
I hadn't expected I could be in
this sort of relationship with you.
What sort of relationship?
A relationship we can touch each other.
We did touch each other, but I...
You don't trust your heart with me
the way you trust your heart with her.
It hurts me.
That's for sure!
I've been with her much longer than you.
I wanna protect her.
I wanna be her hero,
or rather, her IDOL!
That costume is...
I found it in our clubroom.
Hey, are you afraid of this costume?
Your camera isn't running!
Akari, let's film the next part!
Wait!
Where are you going?
I want to film only with her!
I want to make the picture best.
And I brought a camera of my own!
I won't let you do that!
You can't film a movie
without the director's observation!
Director, you want your actresses
to let her heart be naked, don't you?
I think I can do it now.
I feel the same way as you did
when you were filming that idol movie.
No.
That idol movie....
NO!!
Akari, are you all right?
Yes.
You can start.
Okay.
Now, take one.
Here we go.
Take one.
Ready, action!
Akari.
Since I transferred to your junior-high,
I had been bullied.
But you'd protected me.
Thank you.
I would have killed myself if it hadn't been not for you.
Really?
It's a secret.
Did you lick a throat candy?
I feel so embarrassed.
What's that?
The kissing has started.
I had a sort of instinct.
You're so soft.
You kiss me too much.
I have lost.
Director, she has turned me down.
I'm done with this movie, so I'm leaving.
Wait! Are you running away?
I'm not running away.
I'm filming a new movie.
I'm going to...
I, a backseat player of the human race,
will film a spin-off movie of me.
I had, ever since I was born,
I had lived as a female...
with a quite uneasy feeling.
My heart and my body contradict each other.
When I get home,
I change into clothes that I feel the most comfortable.
Men's clothes.
Hello?
Do you have some time now?
Do you remember the factory we went together?
Yes.
I want to talk with you about our future.
She's the one who made fool of me.
This is Kazuko in the first grade and Moe.
Sorry to have called you all of a sudden.
What is that camera?
I brought this for filming.
I'm gonna film the action you rejected
when I confessed my feelings long ago.
What is it? It's revolting!
I'm gonna kiss you.
No! Stop...
The kiss you rejected.
This has made the movie mine.
Stop!
Looks like she's not answering.
I wonder what's the matter with her.
I'm worried.
No!
Sorry, but I need you to help me with the filming.
I'll go on kissing you until you obey me!
Akari, I have made a decision.
I will kiss no one but you for the rest of my life.
But you'll get married, won't you?
Well, I'm not joking.
I don't want to go out with a man any more.
Even if I'll have no chance to kiss for the rest of my life,
that's fine with me if I can save it for you.
If I don't do so, I can't face Aki.
Then I too will kiss no one but you, Yoshie!
Oh, you don't have to do that.
This is an offline edition of
what we've filmed so far.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Actually, I'm thinking of stopping filming of this movie.
The production is to be aborted.
Did you call us to say such a nonsense?
If it continues like this,
this movie will only show girls flirting with each other.
What? Do you mean our kiss is just flirting?
We were much more serious about...
Yoshie!
But there is no future.
How dare you! After all, I just despise you!
Yoshie, stop!
You're wrong.
Huh?
You can find something
only after filming what lies beyond kissing.
When I kissed in front of the camera,
something in me has changed.
I feel I've been saddled with
something I can't escape from.
So does our president.
Do you know that
she's not answering our phone calls?
This movie has stirred everyone's fates!
But I think I'd better delete this piece.
No!
Someone's telling me you mustn't.
I heard the voice.
Her voice!
Wow, a psychic motion picture!
I have a rather strong extrasensory perception!
Do you?
This is...
Ayano.
Here we go. Ready, action!
So, why are you filming a parody of idol movies?
Do you like them?
Uh, yes.
I like the kids program you used to appear.
Ah, when I was a child actress.
Yes, so if I were to film a movie,
I wanted to film that sort of...
Then, an impromptu dance will do?
Yes.
Shall I?
Oh, it looks good, so good.
Ayano had worked as a child actress and a model,
and I'd adored her in my high-school days.
I thought, "If I were to make something
for the school festival, I'd film her."
But Ayano had been famous for being selfish,
and she tried to provoke me in every way.
Let me use it!
Okay! Dance!
No.
Do it now.
- I don't want to.
- Hey, don't move!
Quick.
Go ahead.
Shake your body more!
More!
Quick.
Why are you sitting down?
Shake your body more, much more.
Looks good.
Ayano had stirred whole the things completely.
But I have no further movie materials.
I'm sure I had filmed a lot more,
so I think she must have deleted it.
And I only have fragments of memories.
I will never forgive you!
"I will never forgive you,"
that's the final word of her I can recall.
The next day,
Ayano was stabbed by her boyfriend and died.
What happened during the gap of my memory?
The thought of it still haunts me.
That's why you tried to film
a continuation of your movie with Ayano,
filming us as Ayano's substitutes.
I only ended up in imitating Ayano,
and I couldn't fill any gap.
Then you have to complete the movie all the more.
Unless you do so,
I cannot break up with you.
You will continue playing your role to fill the gap.
Let's film it together, all of us!
Right?
Well, there's no choice.
Maybe our president and
the ghost of Ayano will come to us.
Probably!
Hey!
Let's join our hands!
I don't know exactly, but let's do it!
All right.
Me too?
Of course!
Do our best!
Yeah!
Okay, the camera is ready.
Come in.
I really don't like wearing this!
Wow, it really suits Naomi!
Suits her much better than you!
I don't like wearing the same costume as her.
So, Sis, what are we gonna you?
Yoshie, you pretend to be Ayano and bully Naomi.
What a rough direction.
Oh! I sense Ayano's presence.
She must be somewhere around here.
Hey, where is she?
Okay, act as if you let her possess you.
Ready, action!
I'm Ayano.
Do you want me to bully her... like this?
Ouch, it sores me!
How dare you!
Ouch!
You're supposed to be unable to resist Ayano!
You're still yourself, Yoshie. Do perform!
Are you all right?
Looks like Ayano has possessed your sister!
Ayano, do you wanna tell us something?
Film slight revealing of your pants.
Slight revealing of our pants?
Hey, let's show our pants slightly!
Hey, hey!
No, no, no, thanks.
But what we've filmed so far lacks marketability.
- You'll do it, too, Naomi!
- No, no. no. no.
Quick, do it yourself.
Now.
Good, good. Again!
It was good!
The deleted part definitely included
slight revealing of my pants that she forced me.
Even after Ayano has become a dead,
does she want to torture me sadistically?
Slight revealing of her pants... like this?
Do it more!
Like this?
No!
More!
Like this?
No!
No.
Idol costume... all of you.
Idol costume, all of us?
This is weird.
Ayano probably has some sort of grudge against me,
and attempts to punish me.
But now, a strange sense of unity is growing among us.
Here we go, show your pants!
OK, OK, good, good.
All right, have confidence!
Here we go, show your pants!
No!
OK, OK, good, good.
Though I have a grudge against my ex-lover,
I fill uplifted.... Is it because of the costume?
No one in here had been thinking of becoming idols.
I wish if Aki were with us as well.
I wonder where she is right now.
Here we go!
Yes!
Long time no see.
Aki, Moe.
What's this? Why are you dressed like that?
It's been a while.
I'm leading another group to film a spin-off movie.
Now that I got my own clue members,
we're completely separated.
We've been waiting for you,
to complete the movie with you.
Sorry, but we're in the middle of filming.
We'll shear right through you.
Why do you say such a thing?
Can't you come back to us?
Your cells are different from ours.
If you interrupt us, I'll hit you with this camera.
Let us go.
We're location-scouting, too!
It's no use being sentimental.
The climax of filming.
Let's get there without stopping, Sis!
Okay.
Let's replicate the things at our school,
where Naomi had filmed Ayano.
That's the only way. Let's go!
Yeah!
Quick, quick. This way, this way.
In costumes like them,
it's only a matter of time before they're reported.
Why don't we double-book our filming?
We've gathered about ten extras on Twitter.
Okay, let's go.
Yes.
Yuck, I hear footsteps.
He's gone. Now!
Akari, get the camera ready.
Okay.
Sis, close the door.
Yes.
I closed it.
The camera has been set up.
Here we go.
I'll try to torture you without being bashful.
So that Ayano will possess me.
I'll do my best to recall
all the memories I lost, too.
Let's complete the movie
and break free from the curse on us!
So, here we go!
Ready, action!
Clap!
If you're an idol,
why don't you reveal your pants slightly?
For example, like this!
No! It's so embarrassing!
Further, like this!
I feel so embarrassed!
Okay, once again.
The way you feel bashful looks so nice.
I'm sure you can go further.
The way Yoshie tortures me is
getting a lot closer to Ayano.
Let's recall what happened next.
I'm sure she did something more terrible to me.
Why am I directing a reflector board
to my sister turning over my ex-lover's skirt?
For what have I lived so far?
What was the meaning of Ayano's short life?
Let's do it again!
You're too persistent!
I'm not persistent, let's do it again!
It happened again!
What's your next direction?
School... swimsuits....
All... of... you....
You want us to wear school swimsuits?
We must have some extra school swimsuits
in the changing room.
That's it! Let's go!
What's this?
What're you doing?
We're going to kiss you.
Here we go.
Akari!
Hurry to change into school swimsuits, quick!
- Let's go, we must change first.
- No, why does this has to...
Here, this is your reward.
Thank you so much!
- This is just like a hidden camera show.
Go ahead and kiss a lot! - Yes.
Here.
Thanks a lot.
Three thousand yen for one kiss.
Three thousand yen!?
I'll do my best revealing my bikini!
Please work a little more!
Here they are, school swimsuits!
Indeed.
Okay, let's change into them!
Yes.
No! Please, someone, help me!
NO!!
Aki....
Won't you perform in my movie?
I'll make you the heroine.
Stop that.
Stop it. I don't want to drop out in the middle.
You're still one of the main casts of our movie, Aki.
Why don't you join us again in the school swimsuit?
Filming with your friends is a lot more fun
than filming on your own.
No, it's so embarrassing!
Oh, wearing a swimsuit is so embarrassing!
Me, too. But we have to film the next part!
Yes!
Start performing at once!
Ready, action!
That school swimsuit suits you.
No, it's so embarrassing that I can't bear it!
Okay, here we go.
Hey, take off your hands.
It's already being filmed.
It's good, you look so cute. Smile!
Hey, why don't you smile?
It's too embarrassing to do.
Yes, this is the feeling.
Though the school swimsuit
had already brought me to my limit,
Ayano provoked me further.
Hey, how is it?
It's good. You look so cute.
Then I lost my reason and...
I wanna kiss you.
No, I can't.
I decided I'll kiss only one person
for the rest of my life.
The one I can kiss is not you.
Do you understand?
No. No!
Stop, Yoshie! Don't torture Naomi further!
I remembered!
Everything.
I remembered everything!
What's the matter?
Naomi!
Get out of my way!
Maybe I have hurt her.
There she is!
Hey... what's the matter?
Well, have you become serious?
I only teased you, what a fool you are.
Hey, look at the camera again.
Quick.
Hey, look at the camera.
Hey, do look at the camera.
It's so good.
With all the memories having recalled,
I got confused.
Because I had known Ayano had a male lover...
Yes. I'm filming a movie with my junior, Naomi.
Hey!
Hello, Koji. This is Naomi.
Thanks for being with me till morning the other day.
Hey, what do you mean?
- Why do you know Koji?
- Because I was jealous of Ayano,
I stole Koji from her.
Look, this is Ayano's face in fury.
I will...
never forgive you.
I'll never forgive you!
I had been...
fond of you!
At the night when I cast a malice like this on her,
Ayano had a quarrel with her boyfriend,
and was stabbed to death.
I had practically killed her.
Ayano wants me to make atonement for this.
I know it.
I know the best ending for this movie is my death.
I got the camera ready.
Yoshie.
Go, please.
Go and kiss Naomi.
I think your kiss to her will complete this movie.
But...
I've decided that I will kiss no one but you,
and I don't fancy Naomi.
Then you can love her instead of fancying her.
I believe one kiss will release Naomi from the past.
All I have to do is to go beyond the reality, right?
All I have to do is perform Ayano...
to forgive Naomi!
Yes, forgive her with a kiss.
I'll charge my love to you.
Okay, here we go!
I hate this!
No, stop it!
Hey, help me!
Stop it, Yoshie, Yoshie!
Wait!
Stop it, don't touch my club members!
Aki.
Akari.
Leave them to me.
The role to protect Yoshie needs to be played by me.
Thanks.
Thank you.
No! I mustn't be possessed by the ghost!
Naomi!
Reveal your pants slightly!
The ghost possesses me when I turn to Naomi!
I can't help her!
Yoshie!
Sister!
Quick, use this camera,
and kiss Naomi!
I had once wished Naomi's death,
but when she's actually dying,
I don't want her to.
Even if she's to be kissed by my sister,
I'd rather want her to if she will be saved.
The fight against the ghost has told me...
that this is love.
Sis, is this love?
I can feel it!
Yoshie, quick!
Thanks, everyone.
All the jealousy and grudge have gone.
And only love remains!
Yoshie, we'll handle all the kisses here!
All right, all right....
I'll hang myself.
I'll hang myself!
Don't do that!
NO!!
No, I won't let them arrive at a happy ending!
Wait!
Naomi!
Naomi, you mustn't die.
I will not be able to quarrel with you,
and I don't dislike you.
Naomi, I have realized.
Ayano doesn't want to torture you.
She wanted you to be released
from the trauma of the sense of guilt.
I'll just try to live for now.
I think that's a good idea.
Okay, cut!
Okay, all the filming has been completed!
Great!
Congratulations!
Yes!
Yeah!
Sis, Akari, thanks a lot!
I think I got rid of the ghost.
Oh, that's good.
I'm relieved!
I've been so worried!
It was a great success!
Senpai.
I brought the camera.
Let's film it together.
It's not focused.
Oh, now it's focused.
It looks nice.
Yeah!
Yeah.
We're meeting during the break.
What shall we do?
Today?
Okay, this is our final part.
Hey, what are you gonna do next?
This is our idol movie,
so we'll film a curtain call of our gratitude.
If you're idols, don't you have to wear makeup?
We don't have to,
because we are...
Together!
We're No Makes!
Let's salute!
I'm humbled for being like this
Though there're hundreds of
millions of girls in the world
I'm sorry for being a little subservient
A pose of gratitude to your warm heart
Yes, salute, salute!
Yes, salute!
I salute every time,
I show respect everywhere
I voluntarily ban
it from time to time
I have to self-control!
I give my loyalty to your favors
Yes, salute!
A profound salute!
I salute every time!
I show respect everywhere,
I make a silent prayer occasionally
A silent prayer?
I'm gonna protect you
A one-to-one battle of fancies
Yes, salute! Salute!
Sa-lu-lute! Love! Love, love, yeah!
Fancies! Come, come, yeah!
Bring it on me!
Sa-lu-lute! Love! Love, love, yeah!
Fancies! Come, come, yeah!
Yes, salute!
I had thought it's a sin for
someone like me to fall in love
To me who don't fit
in the world of love and fancies
You have given a smile
You have the kindest
heart in the world
I toss you into the air
before knowing it
And show you a pose of respect
Yes, salute! Salute!
I'm humbled for being like this
Though there're hundreds of
millions of girls in the world
I'm sorry for being
a little subservient
A pose of gratitude to
your warm heart
Yes, salute, salute!
Yes, salute!
The screen comes to an end
to a trashy film
leaving a trail of warmth
the audience begins to leave
a dazzling glow
left behind
don't get up during credit rolls
because the vision remains smiling
if only you could stay and watch me
from the film's end
shall tomorrow come
every one of us plays
the lead of a role called "myself"
a roadshow without a release
still the film goes on
don't get up during credit rolls
the past shivers
if only you could look and find me
hiding love in this trifle ending
don't get up during credit rolls
don't leave me alone
if only you could stay and watch me
from the film's end
shall tomorrow come
tomorrow will come
English subtitles by
Seiko Tanaka / Shinsuke Matsuda